孩子们,你们知道那张在敦煌的照片么?
Kids, you know that photo In the den?
回溯到2006年 外公外婆来看我, 我们出去共享早餐
It was taken back in 2006,when grandma and grandpa came to visit me and we all went out to brunch.
我们看上去都很高兴, 是吗?
We all look pretty happy,right?
错
wrong.
我希望你的脸最好融化掉
I wish your face would melt off.
我还希望你的眼球最好爆炸
I wish your eyeballs would explode.
我讨厌你
I hate you.
我更加讨厌你
I hate you more.
我会杀了他的
I'm going to kill him.
我不能责怪你
I can't say I blame you.
不, 我是认真的
No,I mean I'm seriously going to kill him.
我不管你有多不愿意
I don't care how unpleasant it is.
你必须和他谈谈
You have to talk to him.
但是不是现在
Not now.
好吧, 你不去我去
Okay,if you don't,I will.
Robin...
好吧, 要理解这些东西 你必须知道, 这个故事有3个部分
okay,for any of this to make sense,you got to understand,there are three parts to this story.
那我们就先从Marshall和Lily的部分开始好了
Let's start with the marshall and lily part.
Marshall和Lily的部分
marshall and lily part
作为30周年纪念的礼物 我让我的父母到纽约来度周末
As a 30th anniversary gift,I had flown my parents to new york for the weekend.
哦忘了和你说了 你堂弟Jimmy很喜欢那个温泉
Oh,I forgot to tell you,your cousin jimmy had a wonderful time at that spa he visited.
你是说法官让他去戒毒的那个温泉?
You mean the spa the judge ordered him to go to to quit cocaine?
要咖啡吗?
Coffee?
外婆和外公不喜欢讨论任何不愉快的 太感性的或者说是任何真实的事情
Now,grandma and grandpa didn't like to talk about things that were uncomfortable,emotional,or in any way...real.
嗨, Mosby先生, 夫人
Hi,mr.And mrs.Mosby.
哦, Lily!
Oh,lily!
嗨, Marshall
Hi,marshall.
见到你很高兴
Good to see you.
我只是过来收拾一下自己的东西
I was just stopping by to pick up some of my things.
我们很抱歉你的...
Yes,we were so sorry to hear about your...
你知道...
you know,the,the...
好吧...
well...
Lily把我甩了, 为了逃婚的事情?
lily calling off the wedding and dumping me?
我请求Marshall重修旧好 然后他拒绝了我的事情?
Me begging marshall to take me back and him rejecting me?
我很喜欢你的发型
I love your hair.
sync:fisherchen www.ydy.com
www.ydy.com proudly presents
自从Marshall和Lily分手之后 这是他们的第二次见面
This only the second time Marshall and lily had seen each other since breaking up,
但是正如他们保证的那样 情况也并不是那么尴尬
but to their credit,it wasn't that awkward.
事实上, 我们很好
Actually,we're cool.
我刚才分了一下唱片
We just divided up cds.
都是些本土歌手唱的
It was all very civil.
我为我们而感到骄傲 现在这样很好
I'm proud of us; we're,we're good.
我们8点去Casa A Pezzi吃饭
Well,we were all going to go to casa a pezzi at 8:00.
要不要和我们一起去, Lily?
Lily,would you like to join us?
什么?
what?
如果这会让你们不舒服的话 我看还是算了
Well,I-I don't want to go if it would make you uncomfortable.
怎么会呢?
Why would it?
我是说, 我们...
Well,I mean,yeah,we're...
我们现在这样是很好 但是我们之间还是有点那个什么
we're good,but you got to admit there's that stuff between us.
我不觉得
Um,not for me.
我们现在看上去就像是朋友
Now it's just like we're friends.
就像是兄妹一样
It's like we're brother and sister.
"兄妹"?
"Brother and sister"?
好吧
Okay.
好吧, 等会在餐馆见, 哥哥
Fine,yeah,I'll see you at the restaurant,bro.
看到没?
See?
一点也不尴尬吧
Not awkward at all.
各位好啊
Lily: Hello,everyone.
嗨
Hi.
好啊, Marshall
Hello,marshall.
Lily, 这裙子太棒了
Lily,that is a stunning dress.
哦谢谢
Oh,thanks.
我想你应该还没忘吧 但是我觉得我们是一家人, 是吗哥哥?
It's kind of revealing,but I thought,"hey,we're all family.Right,bro?
这是怎么了?
What's wrong?
哦, 我今天做瑜珈的时候伤到脚踝了
Oh,I,I hurt my ankle in yoga today.
教练让我用深呼吸忍痛, 只是...
The instructor told me to just take deep breaths to get through the pain,just...
你还好吗?
are you all right?
你好像在流汗啊
You're kind of sweating.
没有, 我很好
No,I'm fine.
只是...
It's just...
这东西太辣了
this roll is really spicy.
Lily太可恶了!
Lily is evil!
她穿了那个裙子来折磨我
She just wore that dress to torture me.
好吧, 这个游戏有两个人的份
Well,you know what?Two can play at that game.
看着吧, 就早餐的时候 我会好好折磨Lily一番
See,at brunch,I'm going to torture lily right back.
是的
Yeah.
我身上也有一地方是她的弱点
There's a part of my body that she's got a weakness for,too.
嘿, 你不能在早餐的时候说这个(暗指Marshall的Ding-Dong)
Dude,you can't whip that out at brunch.
不, 不是那个
No,not that.
我要露露我的小腿
I'm going to unleash my calves.
这太变态了
That's crazy.
没人会因为男人的小腿兴奋
Nobody's turned on by men's calves.
他们完全没有性暗示
They're a thoroughly unerotic body part.
我必须说 如果我也像这样小的鸡腿的话
Well,yeah,I'd say that,too,if I had those skinny little chicken legs.
我会等你打电话来道歉的
I'll be waiting by the phone for your apology.
然后Marshall就在早餐的时候用了这个计划
So marshall showed up at brunch with a plan.
你好
Hello.
哦, 嗨
Oh,hi.
嘿, Marshall
Hey,marshall.
怎么样?
How are you feeling?
你昨晚看上去有点狂热
You looked kind of feverish last night.
哦不, 我感觉很好
Oh,no,I actually feel great.
这里好像挺热的, 不是吗?
It is kind of warm in here,though,isn't it?
哦我不清楚 只是有点...
Oh,I don't know,if anything,it's kind of...
你在干什么?
what are you doing?
哦没什么
Oh,nothing.
没什么
Nothing at all.
只是让自己坐的更加舒服一点
I'm just making myself feel a little bit more...comfortable.
哦很好
Oh,yes.
我最近一直在做手指按摩, 所以...
I've been doing all these toe lifts lately,and so...
我的小腿已经紧绷多了
my calves have really been cramping up.
把你的衬衫脱了
take off your shirt.
剩下的裤子也脱了
Take off the rest of your pants.
我真没想到会发生这个
I really wasn't expecting that to happen.
我也没想到
Yeah,me neither.
这好像有点复杂了, 不是吗?
It kind of complicates things,doesn't it?
是的
Yeah,it does.
你为什么要露你完美的小腿给我看?
Why did you have to throw your magnificent calves at me?
你知道你有一副船夫的腿
You know you have a punter's leg.
那你为什么要把你的胸部给我看?
Well,why did you have to throw your beautiful boobs at me?
你知道你有...胸部
You know you have...boobs.
说白了吧, 你来这里只是为了引诱我
Just admit it,you came here trying to seduce me.
我引诱你? 是你在引诱我吧
Seduce you?You seduced me.
你坐在我边上 然后都快把裤子脱光了
You sat down next to me and took most of your pants off.
你去了旧金山3个月
You went to san francisco for three months.
那个怎么能引诱的了你啊?
How is that seducing you?
好吧, 那并没有 但是我还是很生气
Well,it's not but I'm still mad about it.
好吧, 就这样吧 我要Beatles诗选
All right,that's it-- I want the beatles anthology.
太糟糕了, 我并不打算给你
Oh,well,that's too bad; I'm keeping it.
那你还记得我给你的U2的盒子吗?
And you know the u2 box set I gave you?
看看, 都是Dave Matthews
Look inside-- all dave matthews.
你真可恶
You are evil.
笑一个
Smile.
我要杀了他
I'm going to kill him.
我不能责怪你
I can't say I blame you.
不, 我是说我真的想杀了他
No,I mean I'm seriously going to kill him.
接下来让我们说说Barney的部分好了
Now let's talk about the barney part of the story.
Barney的部分
the barney part
这是Robin第一次见我的父母 所以我们俩都有点紧张
This was going to be robin's first time meeting my parents,so we were both a little nervous.
Barney, 你在这里做什么?
barney,what are you doing here?
我在这里等见家长
I'm here to meet your parents.
听了你说的关于Barney的传奇故事之后 他们肯定迫不及待的想见到我
They must be dying to meet me after all the legendary barney stories you've told them.
我没告诉他们一点你的传奇故事
I haven't told them any legendary barney stories.
什么?
What?
Barney, 这里列了我告诉父亲的所有东西 棒球
Barney,here is a list of all the things I talk with my dad about: Baseball.
但是我是你最好的朋友
But I'm your best friend.
事实上, Marshall是我...
Well,actually marshall's my...
我是你生命中最重要的人
I'm the most important person in your life.
事实上Robin是...
Well,robin's actually...
你父母怎么能不知道我呢?
How could your parents not know about me?
我可是很会耍宝的
I'm delightful.
对于我们而言, 当然是, 不过也就这么一点
To us,sure,in very small,infrequent doses.
我是说, 拜托, 你不是那种 父母希望自己孩子交的朋友
I mean,come on,you're not exactly the kind of friend parents want their kid to have.
哦是吗?
Oh,really?
那我相信你穿的这鞋子 不是你今天犯的最大的错误
Then I guess those shoes aren't the thing you're most wrong about today.
嘿, 妈妈
hey,mom.
- 嘿, 老爸 - Ted
Hey,dad. Ted.
- 我知道你们一定很想见到... - Barney Stinson
I know you've all been excited to meet... barney stinson.
很荣幸见到你们
An honor to meet the two of you.
那个绣了"保佑这个邋遢鬼"的枕头是你做给Ted的吧 做的真是太好了
That needlepoint "bless this mess" pillow you made for ted-- what a stitch.
沉默的孩子(Stitch的另外一个意思)! 那刚才那个算什么?
Stitch!Did that just happen?
哦, 老爸老妈 这是我的女朋友, Robin
Uh,mom,dad,this is my girlfriend,robin.
你好
Hello.
见到你真是太棒了, Robin
Oh,it's wonderful to meet you,robin.
你真漂亮
Oh,you are so pretty.
不是吗, Al?
Isn't she pretty,al?
当然
A real looker.
说来好笑 我今天甚至没有照过镜子呢
That's funny,I didn't even "look" in the mirror today.
当我没说
That's not anything,is it?
我在San Marino订了位子 晚上8点的
So,I made a reservation at san marino tonight for 8:00.
San Marino
San marino.
你说真的?
Oh,you're serious?
哦算了吧
Yikes.No.
我们还是试试Casa A Pezzi
We have to try casa a pezzi.
那里的鲑鱼调味饭真是棒极了
Best salmon risotto I have ever had.
我爱鲑鱼调味饭
I love salmon risotto.
我知道
I know.
我们怎么在Casa A Pezzi订到桌子?
How are we supposed to get a table at casa a pezzi?
他们只接受提前几周的预定
They're booked for weeks.
你真是幸运 我认识那里的服务经理, 真是讽刺...
Well,lucky for you,I happen to know the head waitress,which is ironic because...
真是讽刺因为我们都在同一个地方服务
ironic because we both work at a homeless shelter where i serve the food.
你在哪里高就, Robin?
where do you volunteer,robin?
你到底是怎么回事?
What's the matter with you?
我是他女朋友 我正努力表现的很好
I'm his girlfriend,and I'm not even trying that hard.
能得到他们一些好感, 你个笨蛋
Way to wreck the curve,kiss-ass.
Robin, 我是他最好的朋友
Robin,I'm his best friend.
这是我应该做的
That's a commitment.
女朋友, 就像是一场感冒
Girlfriend,that's like a bad flu.
在床上躺上几周就完全不受你的摆布了
Out of your system after a couple weeks in bed.
击掌
High five.
我能帮上什么吗?
Can I help?
当然, Virginia
Yes,you can,virginia.
这件外套背后肯定有一个故事 我想听听
There's a story behind that broach,and I'm going to hear it.
哦, 你真是问对了
Well,funny you should ask.
好啊, Barney
Bravo,barney.
这是我一直都很喜欢的奏鸣曲
That is my all-time favorite sonata.
Barney, 你真讨人喜欢
Barney,you are just delightful.
不, Virginia, 你很讨喜 我只是讨Ted的喜
No,virginia,you're delightful,I am deligh-ted.
Ted就在那里
And he's just ted.
我可没有事先安排什么 真是巧了
I'm really not planning these things; they just keep happening.
呜哦
whoops.
我想我把一冰块掉进去了
I think I dropped an ice cube down here.
哇哦, 好冷啊
Ow,it's so cold.
好吧, 我想我要走了
All right,that's it,I'm out of here.
1分钟后
In a minute.
谁要去Maclaren喝一杯?
Anyone up for a drink at maclaren's?
不了, 我有点累了
No,I'm kind of tired.
我也是
Me,too.
是啊, 我也觉得他们想要...
Yeah,I'm sure my folks are gonna want...
我想我能带一些Cerveza(墨西哥的一种酒)回去
I feel like I could knock back a few cervezas.
Cerveza?
Cervezas?
他吃错药了?
Did he fall?
我也加入 不过我明天得早起
I'd join you,too,but I want to get up early for mass tomorrow.
8点45分在St.Peter教堂是吗? 这是我最爱的仪式
St.Peter's,8:45 A.M.,It's my favorite service.
等等 你能进教堂了?
Wait a minute-- you're able to cross the threshold of a church?
我会给你留一个位子的
I'll save you a seat.
哦, 你真是太棒了
Oh,you are just terrific.
不是吗, Susan?
Isn't he,susan?
Robin
Robin.
Susan, 她叫Virginia
Susan,her name is virginia.
伙计, 我现在真想好好教训你一下你父亲
Dude,I am sincerely ticked at your dad right now.
为什么?
Why?
昨天晚上我们不是一起去Maclaren喝酒了吗?
Last night,we go to maclaren's for a drink,right?
然后Barney冲进火房 举起压着我的冰箱, 把我救了出去
So barney darts back into the burning house,lifts up the refrigerator I'm pinned under and pulls me to safety.
你真是个英雄
You're like a hero.
哦算不上什么英雄, Wendy
Oh,I'm no hero,wendy.
你知道谁是吗?
You know who is a hero?
我的达尔马提亚伙伴, Smokey
My dalmatian,smokey.
他...没能...没能逃出来
He...didn'T...make it out.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真可怜, 伙计
You poor,brave man.
为什么你不给他一个拥抱呢?
Why don't you give the guy a hug?
我...
I'M...
我老爸给你做媒?
My dad was your wingman?
我的脑子现在一团乱
This is really messing with my head.
Barney, 我老爸酷不?
Barney,is my dad cool?
我还没说完
I'm not done.
然后你老爸留在那里接着喝 我提早回去了, 因为第二天要和你妈妈一起早起
So,your dad stays to finish his drink,but I take off because I have to be up early for mass with your mom.
当然
Sure.
我发现我的手机忘在那里了 所以我回去拿...
Anyway,I realize that I left my phone on the bar,so I come back...
哦我的天啊
oh,my god.
这真的是...
Is that really...
哦我的天啊!
oh,my god!
我知道
I know.
你能相信你爸爸给我带了绿帽子吗?
Can you believe your dad rack-jacked me like that?
我爸爸和女服务生Wendy有一手?
My dad made out with wendy the waitress?
他欺骗了我妈妈
He cheated on my mom?
不, 这不可能
No,that's impossible.
Ted, 根据调查 有83%的男人在结婚后6个月就在外面有一手
Ted,it's a well-known statistic that 83% of people married longer than six months are seeing someone on the side.
你知道吗? 你每次举例子的时候用的都是83%这个数字
Do you know that when you make up a statistic,you always use "83%"?
你觉得我在说谎?
You think I'm lying.
好吧, 你有做过关于这个的调查吗?
Well,have you done any surveys on the subject?
在www.时髦的人.婚姻出轨是天性.org 这个网站上就有人做过调查
Because the good people at www.Swingers.Open-marriage-is natural legalize-polygamy.Org have,
他们一开始也不相信
and they beg to differ.
根本就没这个网站
That's not a real web site.
哦我真希望我没有得到他们网站的VIP体恤
Oh,and I suppose I didn't get a real t-shirt for running in their 10k.
嘿, 老爸
hi,dad.
嘿, Ted
Hey,ted.
Barney
Barney.
旅途还算愉快吗?
Ted: Enjoying your vacation so far?
哦是的
Oh,yeah.
听着, 我能和你去外面谈会儿吗?
Uh,listen,can I speak to you outside for a sec?
当然
Sure.
你昨天晚上和Baryney一起出去了?
So you went out with barney last night?
是的
Yeah.
你玩的很开心?
You have a good time?
哦当然
Oh,yeah,yeah.
真可惜你没有来
Sorry you couldn't join us.
是的
Yeah.
那么...
So...
什么?
what?
好吧...
Well...
什么好吧?
well what?
你觉得Cerrano(棒球队员)转到打点位能成功吗?
You think cerrano's got a shot at the rbi title?
我想向他证实的, 但是我做不到
I wanted to confront him,but I couldn'T.
我想我也带了"不谈任何不愉快的事情"的基因
I guess I got the let's-not-talk-about- anything- uncomfortable gene.
好吧, 你没有遗传你父亲的"速战速决"的基因 那是肯定的
Well,you didn't get your dad's close-the-deal gene,that's for sure.
笑笑
Smile.
很好
Great.
我不管这有多不舒服
I don't care how unpleasant it is.
我要你现在就和他谈谈
You have to talk to him.
现在不行
Not now.
好吧, 你不说我说
Okay,if you don't,I will.
Robin...
好吧, 现在我们从头开始 说说我和Robin的部分吧
Okay,now I got to back up all the way to the beginning to tell you the me and robin part of the story.
我和Robin的部分
the me and robin part
我们正随时准备迎接父母的到来
We were expecting my parents at any minute.
关于我妈妈的最后一点
One last thing about my mom.
她审问我每一任女友 我们什么时候结婚, 什么时候生小孩
She grills every single one of my girlfriends about when we're gonna get married and have kids.
但是这是她第一次见到我
But this is the first time she's meeting me.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
如果她提到我的堂妹Stacy, 就说明她准备发问了 Stacy在5年内生了6个孩子
And you'll know it's coming when she mentions my cousin stacy-- six kids in five years.
基本上那个女人已经不成人样了
The woman's basically a ride at a water park.
但是我根本不打算结婚生子
But I don't want to get married and have kids.
我要怎么回应啊?
What am I supposed to say?
你知道吗?
You know what?
你是一个有主见的成人了
You're an adult with perfectly valid opinions.
你不用为此向他们道歉
You shouldn't have to apologize for them.
我得撒谎了
I'm gonna lie.
我来说
I would.
谢谢你给了我U2的盒子
Thanks again for letting me have the u2 box set.
我知道那个对你多重要
I know how important it is to you.
我那天和你Caroline姨妈聊天的时候
I talked to aunt caroline the other day.
她说Stacy又怀孕了
Stacy's pregnant again.
哦, 好消息
Oh,good for her.
那么, 亲爱的...
So,dear...
说说你做记者的趣闻吧
oh,boy.Tell us what it's like being a journalist.
我还没准备好
I'm just not ready.
好吧, 别有压力
Okay.No pressure.
嗯, 我以为你要...
Uh,I thought you,um...
工作很好
it's great.
很好
Good.
现在要把重心放在工作上 毕竟你的直接生涯已经快要结束了
Focus on your job now,because your career clock is ticking.
然后好好准备结婚生子 其他的都暂时放一下吧
There's time for marriage and kids and all that other stuff later.
哦, 有钢琴!
Ooh,a piano!
昨天晚上你还真是逢凶化吉啊?
Ted: You lucked out with my mom last night,huh?
松了口气是吗?
What a relief,right?
当然
Oh,absolutely.
真高兴知道我是一个你妈妈 不想你和我有孩子的女朋友
Whew,what a relief it is to know I'm the one girlfriend your mom doesn't want you to have kids with.
那我是要说太棒了?
Hooray?
我是说, 她是不是认为只有你那个高中女友Cheryl 才能和你生出像样的孩子?
I mean,did she really think that your college girlfriend cheryl would pop out attractive children?
因为我看过她的照片 她的额头就像是山洞怪人似的
'Cause I've seen pictures,and,I'm sorry,that girl had a brow ridge like a caveman.
拜托, 她的额头正好对着光线
Come on,she was just frowning under direct light.
另外, 我不单单不喜欢她这点 还有她的...
And besides,that's not even what I liked about her.It was her...
似乎无关紧要了
it's not important.
Marshall和Lily怎么回事?
What happened to marshall and lily?
他们最近一直都在吵
They've been fighting lately.
也许又跑到什么地方吵去了吧
They're probably off somewhere going at it.
加点咖啡吗?
More coffee?
哦不了, 谢谢
Oh,no,thank you.
她真是不错啊?
Isn't she sweet?
如果她不错 那让她和Ted生孩子好了
Well,if she's so sweet,maybe she should have ted's babies.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
没什么
Nothing.
等1分钟
Lily: Just a minute.
也许不用
Marshall: Maybe less.
Robin, 亲爱的
Robin,dear.
我说了什么让你不开心的话了吗?
Did I say something to upset you?
你为什么不希望我有你的孙子?
Why don't you want me to have your grandkids?
你要让我抱孙子了?
Do you want to have my grandkids?
不!
No!
我是说, 我也不知道
I mean,I don't know.
我只是...
I just...
我要你觉得我是想要有你的孙子的
I want you to want me to want to have your grandkids.
当然
And you should.
我是一座基因金山
I'm a genetic gold mine.
没有家族糖尿病或是心脏病史
No family history of diabetes or heart disease.
所有的人都没有蛀牙 视力都极佳
Everyone has nonporous teeth and perfect eyesight.
我有一个患精神分裂的叔叔 但是得的也是很高级的种类
I had one schizophrenic uncle,but even he had perfect vision.
虽然对于他生活着的那个镇的人来说很不幸 但是他还是一个好人
Which was unfortunate for the people around the bell tower he was in,but still he w a very fine man,and...
抱歉
excuse me.Sorry.
不知道已经排队等了
Didn't know that there was a line.
Marshall你的拉链
Marshall,your zipper.
Robin, 不是我不想要孙子
Robin,it's not that i don't want grandkids.
我只是不认为每个人都要犯 过早结婚这个错误的
It's just I don't think anyone should make the mistake of getting married too young.
你怎么这么说?
Why do you say that?
我是说, 你很早就结婚了
I mean,you got married pretty young.
那并不是一个错误
That wasn't a mistake.
难道是?
Was it?
好吧, 有些事情你并不知道
okay,there's something you don't know.
笑一个
Smile.
我希望你的脸最好化掉
I wish your face would melt off.
我想你的眼球最好炸掉
I wish your eyeballs would explode.
我要杀了他
I'm gonna kill him.
我不管这有多不舒服 但是你必须和他谈谈
I don't care how unpleasant it is,you have to talk to him.
现在不行
Not now.
好吧, 你不说我说
Okay,if you don't,I will.
Robin..
Robin...
哦天啊 让我来帮帮你, 亲爱的
Oh,gosh,let me help you pick those up,sweetheart.
亲爱的?
Sweetheart?
你心中唯一一个亲爱的 应该是和你在一起30年的女人
The only sweetheart in your life should be the woman you married 30 years ago,
不是昨晚在酒吧的那个 不是这个笨手笨脚的荡妇
not the waitress at the bar last night and not this clumsy floozy!
抱歉, 我不是说你是荡妇
I'm sorry,you're not a floozy.
我很郁闷 我都不知道自己再说什么
I'm upset,I don't know what I'm saying.
但是, 离我爸爸远点
But stay away from my dad.
Ted, 你在说什么?
Ted,what are you talking about?
老爸?
Dad?
你应该告诉妈妈昨天晚上在酒吧的事情了吧?
You,uh,want to tell mom what happened at the bar last night?
好吧
Okay.
我和一个女服务生亲热了
I hooked up with a waitress.
我是说, 哦!
I mean,oh!
等我们回去了要好好谈谈, Al
We're going to have a serious talk about this when we get home,al.
好好谈谈? 妈妈, 怎么...
Serious talk?Mom,what...
他和另外一个女的接吻啊
He was kissing another woman.
你一点都不在乎?
Don't you care?
Mosby夫人?
Mrs.Mosby?
Ted, 我们不知道到底该怎么告诉你...
Ted,we weren't quite sure how to tell you this...
你妈妈和我离婚了
your mother and i are divorced.
你们...
You...
你们离婚了是什么意思?
what do you mean you're divorced?
什么时候的事情?
Since when?
哦, 差不多9个月了吧
Oh,gosh,it's been about nine months now.
快10个月了
Closer to ten,I think.
时间过的真快
Time flies.
也就是说10个月前 你们突然决定瞒着我离婚了?
so ten months ago,you just up and decided to get divorced without telling me?
不, 这不是一时的决定
No,it wasn't a snap decision.
我们已经差不多分居2年了
We'd been separated almost two years.
你们怎么什么都没告诉我?
How could you not tell me this?
我们想说的, 但是一直没有找到合适的机会
We meant to,it just never seemed like the right time.
那么去年圣诞节...
So last christmas...
我们想告诉你的 但是发现那样就破坏圣诞气氛了
We talked about telling you kids then,but it didn't seem very christmasy.
我给你们买的协力自行车呢?
I got you a tandem bike.
哦, 那个没有浪费
Oh,it didn't go to waste.
你妈妈和Frank一直都在骑
Your mother and frank ride it all the time.
谁是Frank?
Who the hell is frank?
哦, 一个很不错的家伙
Oh,great guy.
我的确挺喜欢他的
I actually set them up.
你还记得Muchnik医生吗?
You remember dr.Muchnik.
他帮你做的矫正
He did your braces.
好吧, 我的头要炸了 我不想和你们多说什么, 我走
Okay,my head's about to explode,and I don't want to get it all over everyone's waffles,so I am leaving.
Teddy宝贝, 哦...
Teddy bear,oh...
他昨天晚上提过他已经离婚了
you know,he mentioned he was divorced last night.
我完全忘记这回事情了
I totally spaced on that.
哦, 煎蛋处没有队伍
Ooh,no line at the omelet station.
Lily...
很抱歉我刚才说了那些话
I'm sorry that I said all those things.
我也是
Me,too.
我都不知道怎么呆在你身边了
I just find it really confusing to be around you right now.
我也一样
It's the same for me.
我想我们还是保持一段距离吧
I think we're probably both better off trying to keep some distance for a while.
我也这么觉得
Yeah,I think you're right.
你穿了提胸内衣了?
Are you wearing a push-up bra?
你魔法晒过你的小腿?
Did you mystic tan your calves?
我收回我的问题
I withdraw the question.
我们很抱歉没提过离婚的事情
We're sorry we didn't say anything about the divorce.
真不应该瞒着你
It was wrong not to tell you.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是听着, 别告诉你妹妹
But listen,don't tell your sister.
他没法接受这个
It would just upset her.
不, 这太荒谬了!
No,this is ridiculous!
我们要好好谈谈 不单单是棒球
We have to start talking about stuff,and not just baseball.
印第安纳今天赢了
Indians won today on a walk-off double.
对红袜队? 真是一场关键的胜利
Against the red sox? Boy,that's a big win.
不, 不
No.No. No.
别想这么就打发过去
We're not gonna blow past this.
我是说, 我都不知道你们是
I mean,I don't even know who you people.
你们是怎么认识对方的
I don't even know how you met.
我从来没告诉过你怎么和你妈妈认识的?
I never told you how I met your mother?
没有
No.
哦, 很好的一个故事
Oh,great story.
在酒吧
At a bar.
就这样?
That's it?
这就是形成我们这个家庭的过程?
That's what passes for communication in our family?
如果是我, 我会原原本本的告诉我的孩子 我是怎么认识他的母亲的
Man,when I have kids,and I tell them how I met their mother,I'm gonna tell them everything,the whole damn story.
我想想, 应该是一个爱尔兰酒吧
I think it was an irish bar.
我不知道...
I just,I don'T...
我真是搞不懂
I don't understand.
你们看上去很开心
You seemed so happy.
我还是小孩的时候, 你们看上去那么...
When I was growing up,you seemed so...
发生什么事情了?
what happened?
我们只是发现我们并不合拍
We just realized we're very different people.
你父亲就像是飘在天上的浪漫 而我是属于脚踏实地地过日子
Your father's kind of a head-in-the-clouds romantic,and I'm much more down to earth.
那么?
So?
我和Robin也是这样
Robin and i are like that.
这并不能说明什么
That doesn't mean anything.
我想要孩子
I wanted kids.
但是你母亲...
And your mother...
当然也想要孩子
also wanted kids.
Robin和我有着不同的家庭观
Robin and I have different views on families.
我们也不会因为这个而分手的
We're not about to break up because of it.
某程度来说, 我一直都知道
On some level,I always knew.
起初我都不想和他一起出去
I didn't even want to go out with him in the beginning.
但是他花了好几个月求我 我终于屈服了
But he spent months badgering me until I finally gave in.
当你没有考虑过多的基本问题的时候
Well,when you don't connect on that many fundamental levels,
认识到不合拍也只是时间问题了
it's only a matter of time before you realize you're not meant to be together.
但是我们爱Robin
But we love robin.
当然
Absolutely.
看到你就像看到了我的指路明灯
Meeting you was the highlight of my trip.
应该是第二盏灯
Well,second highlight.
我们里面见
We'll see you inside.
抱歉
Sorry.
我知道
I know.
他们爱我!
They love me!
我们的确应该尝试着多多沟通
We are definitely going to try and communicate more.
从现在开始, 毫无保留
From now on,full disclosure.
很好
Good.
很好, 我想这样才像一家人
Good,I think it'll be really good for the family.
对了, 奶奶怎么样了?
By the way,how's grandma?
她没回我好几个电话了
She hasn't returned my last couple calls.
我去拿点橙汁
I'm gonna get some juice.
不
No.
你昨天晚上错过了一场很棒的比赛
you missed a great game last night.
真是振奋人心
Real squeaker.
sync:fisherchen www.ydy.com
www.ydy.com proudly presents